Okay, perfect. Um, well, here's our
local media and we're just going to go
ahead and ask you some questions. So,
let's get started with Todd Lebo.
>> Hey, Peter. First of all, just tell us a
little bit about the phone call you got,
who you talked to, and how exciting that
that was to get drafted tonight.
>> Yeah, I mean, I I got the phone call.
Um, you know, first I talked I took the
GM out, they put Coach Reed on the
phone. I pass the phone to coach back.
We just went down the whole line. I
talked to the whole staff basically. It
was just, you know, I was defining like,
come on, I'm ready to go. Like, let's
go. You know, it was was very emotional.
Uh something that I knew like when the
time came and if I was still there, man,
this this was something that was going
to happen for me. And you know, this is
this is what God wanted for me and I'm
just excited to be a chief.
>> Tell me about that party. Looked like
everyone had the white on. You look
good. What was the theme there?
>> Yeah. So, so originally my vision for
myself was to wear white. Um, and then
so it became kind of a white party
became a thing and then it was like you
can't wear white like everybody else.
This is the trap party. Uh, and then so
the so the thing became white party man.
But all these people here man are part
of my village, you know, and and I hold
and dear my heart and a lot of them if
all of them have everything to do with
this moment for me. I'm just glad that I
can share with all.
We'll go next, Derek.
>> Hey, Peter, congratulations. And well,
>> there you go.
>> Hold on. Oh my god. Okay.
>> Hey, uh I'm First thing I was curious
about was just how much contact did you
have with the Chiefs through the draft
process?
>> Oh, yeah. So the chief like they were,
you know, talking to me the whole draft
process pretty much um met them and
talking to them and they were showing
interest from from the very beginning.
So this was uh something that you know
didn't really come as a surprise more of
a blessing and you know like I said like
when it came big 29 I felt I felt I knew
I knew it was going to be me.
>> And both Andy Reid and and Brett V both
talked about you and having some Aaron
Donald kind of elements to you. Is is
that a guy that you model yourself after
or are there other players in the league
that you've watched and and model
yourself after?
>> I mean, it'd be he's my favorite player
that's ever played a game. Uh so it'd be
crazy for me to say I model my game
after him. But uh couple other guys, you
know, they'll take from like Jeff
Simmons, Williams, uh some of those
guys, you know, who who rely on kind of
their twitch and speed power ratio um
to, you know, create opportunity,
mismatch guys, guys that you can move
down the line. Uh, and so I think that's
what I made to the game.
>> We'll go next to Sam McDow.
>> Hey, Peter. Um, obviously you you played
in in high school and were a pretty top
recruit there, but I just wondered, are
you someone who kind of feels like your
best football's ahead of you? And and if
so, what what leads you to believe that?
>> Um, I'm always a guy that's looking to
be on the rise. Uh, I feel like I'm
never satisfied. I'm never where I want
to be. Um, and if you ask me what I need
to get better at, I probably run you off
a list of things that you probably think
I'm great at. And that's just kind of my
mindset and that's why, you know, I'm
I'm able to be here every day. You know,
speaking you guys and so I'd be crazy if
I got rid of that just because I quote,
you know, there's so much work to be
done. Uh, so much to learn. You know,
I'm blessed to be in in a room with with
veteran Chris Jones and and be under
Andy Reid who who has done it so many
times, you know, and so just the
situation is is probably more of a
blessing than anything else.
>> Well, then then I have to ask what what
what where do you think you can get
better?
>> Um, yeah, I definitely think I get
better like finishing my plays, you
know, tackling fundamentals, uh, then I
wrap up my pass. Um uh and definitely
just you know making sure that I focus
on the real technique and fundamentals
and not really relying on my athleticism
or different things my explosiveness to
make plays because you know when you get
to the next level it's all about
technical fundamentals and and doing it
harder and man from just about
>> let's go next to her top.
>> Hey Peter, welcome to Kansas City man
and congratulations.
>> Thanks.
>> Yeah, you're welcome. You mentioned the
opportunity to learn from Chris Jones
and obviously this is your rookie year.
How much do you see yourself being in
his back pocket picking his brain and
and learning the nuances of what Spags
Spagnola expects from his interior
defensive lineman?
>> Pretty much as he'll let me. Um I think
that I'd be crazy to think I come into a
league that I never played and think I
know everything. I think that I have the
talent, I have the mindset, and I have
the leadership skills and capabilities
to come in and make an impact
immediately. But um we talking about a
hall of famer, you know, future hall of
fame, right? So um I'm going to be a
sponge, you know, from the moment I step
into the door and try to my day any way
possible.
>> What's up, Peter? Congrat U.
>> Can I just hold this? Can I hold this?
>> Is that fine? Can I hold this?
>> Yes.
>> All right. Cool.
>> What's up, Peter? Congratulations, my
man.
>> What's good? Appreciate it, brother.
>> Yes, sir. Uh, man, I read somewhere that
you uh you and your family have watched
the draft every year. What how much
different was it this year for you guys?
>> Man, I got my name called. I think that
was the big difference. You know, I'm
>> there's brothers and stuff, you know,
that that I go through battle with and
guys that I knew like through recruiting
and stuff that get drafted, but it just
hits different when when your name's in
the running. uh you know and and you
know that's just a testament to my hard
work but also you know having my village
around me is a little different because
it's about me you know usually it's just
me and my immediately family u but it
just be crazy just to share that moment
and there were just so many people who
had their hand on me uh through this
whole journey man and and you know I'm
just so grateful for my whole village
>> next to Nick Jacobs
>> and Sydney I'll have a followup if I can
please um Peter for you what is it about
the game that you love and keeps you
coming back to it?
>> Physicality. Um, I love that you can
just hit another grown man in his chest
and and and force him to like it. Ain't
nothing he can do about it. He can't run
from it. He get paid to it. He got a job
to do. Uh, you know what I'm saying? And
and and so you just make a good target.
I put my hands right in there and and
and that's what I do. That's what I
pride myself on. I'd also say a close
second to just how rewarding uh the game
is for preparation. I think I take
preparation very seriously. I prepare,
how I take on every game, uh, every
practice. And I think this game,
especially at the NFL level, it'll
reward you for that. Those guys are
putting that extra work, that extra time
in the field, really make sure that they
learn and and study their opponents. And
and so I'm I'm really excited about that
aspect and seeing what else I can learn
in that regard.
>> And whether it's a coach or parent or
grandparent or whoever, um, who is it
that had some advice that's really stuck
with you that's helped you get to this
point? Uh yeah, I think it would just be
uh my mom just telling me, you know,
keep doing the things that got you here.
You know what I'm saying? Don't get away
from uh the things that got you here.
You know, your humbleness, uh your
hunger, your will to win, your will to
get better. Um you know what I'm saying?
Don't forget where you came from. Don't
forget that little 5-year-old kid who
had the dream of being here, uh and the
dream of not just getting there, but I
was old enough and mature enough to to
know that I had the dream to to succeed
when I got there. Um, and and that's the
biggest thing, man. Like, you know, this
is a blessing. I'm super excited to be a
Chief, but but but the goal is, you
know, Super Bowl goals, uh, rings, you
know, being being productive, uh, being
the best teammate and player for my
team. And, you know, that that's what
I'm shifting my focus to.
>> Last one for you, Peter. Go ahead,
Darren.
>> Thank you. Uh,
thank you. Uh, well, can can you Okay, I
want you. Yeah, I game fun.
>> Okay, just just want to make sure. Uh,
look, first of all, like everyone else,
welcome to Kansas City. Couple of things
for you. You know, coming from Clemson
and being coached by Daboo, how do you
feel like, you know, his coaching style
has prepared you for the league and the
things that you probably heard or if you
haven't heard about Andy Reid's uh
training camps, especially up at St.
Joe? How do you feel like, you know,
what you what you learned on the DABO
will help translate uh your skills to
the NFL?
Um, to be honest, when when it comes to
a training camp or or a preseason, I I
don't think I'll ever go through
anything harder than than than what I
went through at Clemson, man. Like, we
we do it different. And so, uh, from
from that aspect, you know, I'm just I'm
super excited, man. Like, whatever it
is, man, I'm going to take it on head
first. Um, you know, coach me hard, you
know, make make get the best out of me.
You know, this is what I want. I want to
be great. You know what I'm saying? I
want to be the greatest at my position.
So, um, whatever it takes, you know,
from a coaching standpoint, I'm not any
type of player to to, you know, shy away
from no action or or anything like that.
So, so I'm ready for whatever it is,
>> Peter. That's all we have for you,
>> man. Thank you.
>> Thank you so much. And congratulations
again. No sheep.